Every life is a universe all its own.
The Life of Chuck is a fantasy, drama film directed by Mike Flanagan.
In this extraordinary story of an ordinary man, Charles 'Chuck' Krantz experiences the wonder
of love, the heartbreak of loss, and the multitudes contained in all of us.
Charles 'Chuck' Krantz, played by Tom Hiddleston.
Charles 'Chuck' Krantz (pre-teen), played by Benjamin Pajak.
Narrator (voice), played by Nick Offerman.
Marty Anderson, played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Felicia Gordon, played by Karen Gillan.
Sarah Krantz, played by Mia Sara.
The Life of Chuck is a 2024 American fantasy drama film written for the
screen, co-produced, edited, and directed by Mike Flanagan.
It is based on the 2020 novella of the same name by Stephen King.
The film stars Tom Hiddleston, Chiwetel Ejiofor, Karen Gillan, Mia Sara, Carl Lumbly,
Benjamin Pajak, Jacob Tremblay, and Mark Hamill, with narration by Nick Offerman.
The film's plot follows the formative moments in the life of Charles "Chuck" Krantz, chronicled in reverse
chronological order, from his death, which is connected to the end of the universe, to his childhood.
The Life of Chuck had its premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 6, 2024, where it won the People's Choice Award,
and was released in select theaters in the United States by Neon on June 6, 2025, before expanding nationwide on June 13.
The film has grossed $19 million worldwide and
received generally positive reviews.
The film explores themes of slice of life, cancer, death,
based on short story, reverse chronology.
The tone is emotional.